<form theme="light">
  <label>Musubu</label>
  <description></description>
  <row>
    <panel>
      <html>
        <h2>Use Musubu’s unique IP and Network cyber threat scoring and profiling API right in your Splunk instance to determine the following for each IP</h2>
<ul>
  <li>
            <strong>Cyber Threat Score</strong>: A 0-100 rating of how much of a cyber threat the IP may be based on the output of our analytics and algorithms.</li>
  <li>
            <strong>Cyber Threat Classification</strong>: High-Medium-Nuisance-Low rating of an IPs cyber threat potential for quick identification.</li>
  <li>
            <strong>Blacklist Class</strong>: The predominant cyber threat vector seen as associated with the IP address (e.g. Phishing, Ransomware, TOR, etc.).</li>
  <li>
            <strong>Blacklist Count</strong>: The number of major IP blacklisting services that have blacklisted the IP address.</li>
  <li>
            <strong>Blacklist Neighbors</strong>: The number of other IP addresses in the same subnet that have been blacklisted.</li>
  <li>
            <strong>Blacklist Count</strong>: The number of times in the last 90 days the IP address has been blacklisted.</li>
</ul>
<hr/>
        <h1>Getting Started:</h1>
        <p>Below are the steps required to begin using the app.</p>
        <ul>
          <li>
            <strong>Step 1.</strong> Enter your Musubu API Key on the Configuration Tab</li>
          <li>
            <strong>Step 2.</strong> Configure an Input using a single valid IP Address on the Input Tab</li>
          <li>
            <strong>Step 3.</strong> Restart Your Splunk Instance!</li>
        </ul>
<hr/>
<h1>Features:</h1>
<h3>Musubu IP Threat Data Tooltips</h3>
<p>Simply enter an lookup definition file name containing IP data ("ip" as the field name) in the "Enter IP Lookup Definition" and click submit.</p>
<p>The results will show in the table below with mouse over capability for each IP address in the csv lookup file defined.</p>
<br/>
<h3>
          <em>"showipthreatdata"</em> Custom Command</h3>
<p>Leverage the “showipthreatdata” custom command within the add-on to make direct calls to the Musubu API from the Splunk search view.</p>
<ul>
          <li>
  Head over to the Search tab and type this command showipthreatdata <em>ipv4address_goes_here</em>
</li>
        </ul>
      </html>
    </panel>
  </row>
</form>